Be gentle.
Those are cosmetics.
Ms. Liang,
you're finally here.
I've got the guest room ready for you.
How can you let me stay in the guest room?
I should be staying with He Yu, of course.
Silly me.
Since you're He Yu's fiancée,
you must stay with him.
Take Ms. Liang's luggage...
Put it in the Second Young Master's room.
Yes.
Hurry up.
Zhang Xin actually
convinced the Master
to let Liang Chunsheng stay
at the He residence.
Now I have another
stumbling block in my way.
Second Young Master!
He Yu,
why is your room so empty?
You've already taken over.
Of course I have to give
the bedroom to you.
Do you hate me that much?
What do you think?
It doesn't matter.
One day,
I will make you submit to me.
Suit yourself.
Since Miss Liang
has moved into the He family,
she is now
a part of our family.
Yu,
you need to take good care
of Miss Liang from now on.
Yu,
I want to eat that.
Is that enough?
I'm full.
Master,
please calm down.
Have a seat, Miss Liang.
Feelings
need to be nurtured.
Yu is just not quite used to
living with someone else yet.
In my opinion,
it's better to let Mei
spend more time with Ms. Liang.
After all, Mei knows Yu best.
Sure,
I'd be happy to.
Before Xiaoyu and Ms. Liang get engaged,
you must attend to her every need.
How about it?
Wanna compete with me?
What do you want to compete in?
Li Zhangxin,
why are you trying to harm me?
Help!
He Yu,
did you see
how Li Zhangxin treated Miss Liang?
Go save her now!
As you wish.
Are you satisfied?
What else do you want
to compete with me for?
Hero saving the beauty,
I'll do it.
Who is it?
I'm saving you. What's wrong?
Where are you touching me?
He Shi,
let go!
He Shi!
Aren't you afraid the master
will whip you again, He Shi?
Help!
Let go of me!
He Shi!
Help!
He Shi, save me!
Letting you die like this
is too easy on you.
How could you bear
to leave me alone
in this long night?
You blocked me.
Playing hard to get.
I like it.
Why is it you?
Don't you like my bed-warming service?
Get out.
Ms. Liang,
it'd be a pity
if no one appreciates
how beautifully you're dressed.
Roujing,
you did great.
I knew He Shi
couldn't keep it in his pants.
If we give the photos to Dad,
we can kick He Shi out.
Even if we blow this up,
knowing Dad,
he'll just cover it up.
Give them to Zhang Xin.
She'd never guess that
bringing Ms. Liang into the He family
was letting a fox into the henhouse.
Who took this?
I thought after the Master beat you up,
you would have learned your lesson.
I didn't expect
you to be even more brazen.
She seduced me.
I couldn't
control myself.
Do you think I'd believe you?
Let me tell you...
In this house,
even if you're having an affair,
it can only be with me.
Enjoy your meal, Miss.
You put the photo
in my room, didn't you?
I just wanted to let Mrs. He know.
Even if Miss Liang
marries the Second Young Master,
she will always maintain
an underground affair
with the Eldest Young Master.
Do you think He Shi
will still have you in his heart then?
He Shi and I
have had nothing to do
with each other for a long time.
Is that so?
Am I really that outstanding?
Li Zhangxin,
if you hadn't kicked me
out of the He family,
how would I have ended up like this?
Hello,
Mrs. He.
Long time no see.